[cheering]
>> All right. All right.
Sorry. Are you gay?
No. Okay. Sorry. I guess we're allowed
to wear whatever we WANT NOW. OKAY.
>> [laughter]
>> SORRY. I DON'T LIVE IN CALIFORNIA. I
DON'T KNOW THE RULES, OKAY?
It's crazy. No, I love I'm sorry. What's
your name?
>> Noah.
>> Noah. Oh, beautiful. Biblical. Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Wait, Noah, I'm sorry. Have you ever
done any Is this your girlfriend? Oh,
what's your name?
>> Lindsay.
>> Lindsay. Good luck, [\h__\h] But I
>> [laughter]
>> No, I'm just saying Noah, have you ever
done anything gay?
Not even like Not even like jerked off
in the same room as a guy?
Wait, Noah, do you think that two guys
jerking off in the same room together is
gay? Wait, Noah, wait. Picture this,
okay?
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, ready? Everyone picture this.
There's two guys sitting on a couch.
It's not me and you.
>> [laughter]
>> But they look IDENTICAL TO US.
SO, IT'S NOT US, BUT IF anybody took a
picture, they'd be like, "Is that Dylan
and Noah?"
All right. All right. All right. Noah,
they're on the couch. They're not
touching, right? They're not touching.
They're rock hard stroking like, "Oh my
god, it feels so good."
>> [laughter]
>> That's how men jerk off when you girls
aren't around.
All right, Noah, they're not touching,
but every once in a while, they kind of
lean over and look, okay? [laughter]
Is that gay?
>> That's pretty [\h__\h] gay.
>> Okay, I guess
I guess we're not HANGING OUT LATER.
>> [laughter]
>> OH MY GOD, OKAY, THAT'S CRAZY. And
you're not gay? Okay, let's Hey.
>> [laughter]
>> Hey, LET'S UNCROSS THE LEGS.
DON'T ACTUALLY DO IT. DON'T DO IT. NO.
YEAH.
SWEETIE, THAT'S GAY BULLYING. JESUS.
>> [laughter]
>> SORRY. Can I make Can I apologize to you
guys really quickly? I I I'm in a little
bit of a weird mood. I got into a fight
today at the hotel gym. Uh yes, with a
hot woman, obviously. Uh
uh my mortal enemy.
>> [laughter]
>> So, has to take them down. I'll do it.
>> I got into a fight with this woman
because I didn't hold the door for her.
So, I'm not from around here. I don't
know the rules or whatever. Um I'm from
Massachusetts where women hold their own
doors.
>> [laughter]
>> And so, I was walking to the elliptical.
Now, side note, if you use the
elliptical, you're fat. And [laughter]
don't get weird about that. You've never
seen someone on the elliptical with a
ripped body like
>> [laughter]
>> It's the slob machine.
It's for slobs, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> You could use THAT MACHINE EVERY DAY FOR
a year and your body WOULDN'T CHANGE,
OKAY?
>> [laughter]
>> AND BY the way, there I was walking my
fat ass to it. So,
I'm walking and I hear from behind me
this woman's like, "Sir. Sir. Sir. Sir.
I just want to know what kind of man
doesn't hold the door for a woman." I
was like, "Ma'am, I'm gay."
>> [laughter]
>> I'd let you get hit by a car.
Ooh, not a good gay person.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know what the media's been
telling you, but we're not all nice.
Yeah, I also like the inside of the
sidewalk, [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> YOU CAN'T HAVE EVERYTHING YOU can't have
every rack at Marshalls and the inside
of the sidewalk, okay? [laughter]
It's not HOW LIFE WORKS.
I DON'T KNOW IF you can tell, I'm a I'm
a very liberal person. I I really
believe in liberal values. I will say my
mission in life is to make being liberal
cool again. I'm a winner and I want to
start winning elections. And
>> [laughter]
>> I'm at the point now, this is my
perspective. If you're a straight guy
and you believe that like women should
be allowed to have abortions and you
don't like throw up when gay guys kiss,
say the R word. I don't care.
>> [laughter]
>> Have fun. YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN? LIKE I
get it, you know? And I just I like as
liberals, we have to stop attacking each
other for every little mistake that you
make. Just cuz you don't agree with
someone doesn't mean that what they did
is wrong. Like for example, I don't use
chat GPT. I've never used it. Okay,
thank you. Yeah, thanks.
But I got my dog from a breeder.
And
>> [laughter]
>> you can't do everything right. You can't
do everything right. [laughter]
I had a woman get really mad at me when
I said that one time. She was like, "Why
didn't you get your dog from a shelter?"
I was like, "Oh my god, let me explain."
>> [laughter]
>> They don't have King Charles Cavaliers
at the shelter.
Honey, IF THEY HAD KING CHARLES
CAVALIERS AT THE SHELTER, I'd be
volunteering, okay? [laughter]
It's crazy.
Um no, I love that. Noah, have you ever
had a threesome? Actually, wait, Noah,
gun to your head So your wife's here, I
apologize.
Um gun to your head, if you had to have
a threesome, would it be two girls, one
guy, or two guys, one girl?
>> Three guys.
I would hate that [laughter] one.
>> And listen, I think that
I do. I think that you girls deserve to
be able to have sex with each other.
It's just that when I see it with my own
eyes, I feel sick to my stomach.
>> [laughter]
>> There's just too much hair thrashing
around in the two girls, one guy The
girls in those videos ARE ALWAYS LIKE,
>> [laughter]
>> I'M ALWAYS LIKE, "SWEETHEART, PUT IT IN
A PONY. WE'RE AT WORK, OKAY?"
>> [laughter]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING WHIPPING YOUR HAIR
AROUND LIKE THAT, YOU KNOW?
>> [laughter]
>> This might be shocking to you guys, but
um I have recently started watching
straight porn. It's my new
It's my new thing.
Don't worry, I'm not [\h__\h] you up for
the show. But I
Sometimes the girls get a little
confused cuz I'm 6'5". Girls will see me
6'5". You know, it's always a
brunette-haired girl with a middle part
staring at me breathing heavy.
And they're always like,
"I found one."
>> [laughter]
>> And then I start talking and she's like,
"No, fuck." You know.
No, but I have I love watching straight
porn. It's my new thing because cuz
there's a lot of gay guys who walk
around and they say a lot of really
negative things about women's bodies.
Well, they'll be like, "Oh my god, I'm
disgusted with vaginas." And just to be
clear, girls, that's not me. Uh yeah, I
think your vaginas are like so cool.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I love those little pockets you
got, you know?
I'm always like, "Let's put something in
there." And so, uh
I do, I love it. And so, I've been
watching a lot of straight porn. I will
say, from what I'm seeing in the
straight porn, I am really nervous for
you girls. I really hope that you girls
are not having sex the way the girls in
the porn are having sex. Are y'all on
all fours howling like goats like
>> [laughter]
>> Mascara running down your face into your
mouth? I go, "She's crying."
Is that what straight men like? They
like when they [\h__\h] you till you cry?
You guys all get really weird, you're
like, "That is what they like."
>> [laughter]
>> That's bad. No, every time I see a video
of a man [\h__\h] a woman, I'm like,
"This is what men are doing to my
friends."
>> [laughter]
>> The girls I do arts and crafts with,
okay?
>> [laughter]
>> She's folded like a pretzel. I thought
she was a feminist, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> It's not normal.
I've also been watching This is really
going to shock you guys. I've been
watching a lot of straight [\h__\h] porn.
Why? You know, I I'm bored.
I [\h__\h] so many guys and I'm like, I
don't know how the girls doing it, you
know?
>> [laughter]
>> I will say something I've noticed the
girls are doing in the straight [\h__\h]
porn, which I I really get nervous for
you. Are you girls making eye contact
with the guy while you're suck
>> [laughter]
>> Girls,
you have to stop.
Girls, do not look at him in the eyes
when you're doing that. Girls, that's
how evil gets in, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> AND BY THE WAY, I KNOW THAT HE'S ABOVE
you staring down at you like the devil,
like, [laughter] "Look up, my little
princess."
Look up, look up, look up.
>> [laughter]
>> You girls are down there, you're looking
up. It's just his double chin. You're
like, "How did I get here?"
>> [laughter]
>> I'm sure there's some straight guys
right now being like, "Wow, it's a lot
about sucking cock."
>> [laughter]
>> That's the whole show.
I do love giving head. It's probably one
of my favorite um activities. Uh
I love it so much that I've actually
considered opening up a glory hole
before.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, wait, wait, wait. You want to know
what stops me from opening up the glory
hole, honestly? I'm just too damn
chatty.
>> [laughter]
>> There's just no way I wouldn't be at the
hole like, "How's it going?"
>> [laughter]
>> "What do you do for work?" You know?
He'd be like, "Shut up and suck my
cock." I'd be like, "Huh, nobody wants
to connect anymore."
Um
>> [laughter]
>> No, I uh I So, I do have a tip for you
girls if you want it from a gay guy. Not
in like a misogynistic way, like, you
know, some gay guys they walk around and
they say things like, "Oh, you know,
guys give better head." That's not true.
That's gay propaganda. Um that's It is.
That's just something that gay guys say
to try to manipulate your boyfriends
into letting us suck their [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Don't fall for it. Uh-uh.
It's also such a creepy thing to say,
like, "Oh, you know, guys give better
head." It's creepy, you know what I
mean? I never I don't want to be a
creepy gay guy. Like, for example, like
if I wanted to suck off Noah, uh
>> [laughter]
>> I wouldn't say, "Oh, you know, guys give
better head." I'd say,
"Do you want to see my collection of
Jordans?"
>> [laughter]
>> He gets to the house, I don't have any,
you know?
>> [laughter]
>> "What are we going to do now? What are
we going to
Do you LIKE ASSASSIN'S CREED?"
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T HAVE AN XBOX. OKAY. UH
NO, WAIT, but if you want the tip from
me to you from a gay guy who loves
sucking dick, this is my tip. Cuz I know
if I don't know if you've ever heard
this, but a a private investigator once
said that women can feel men looking at
them from over a mile away. Meanwhile,
men will get shot in the head and be
like, "What happened?" So, I know
I know when you're down there, you can
feel him wanting you to look up. That's
what I want you to do. When you're down
there, don't look up, right? Put two
fingers over his eyelids like a dead
body. Okay, like
Like [laughter] you're
Like you're laying to rest a corpse,
right?
Close your eyes.
>> [laughter]
>> Think about your wife.
You know, have you ever seen the videos
of the two guys, one girl, just the
videos? No? Oh, you're in so much luck.
I'll explain them.
>> [laughter]
>> So, there's two different kinds of
male-male-female threesomes. There's the
kind of the guys they're so straight.
They're like Noah. They won't even like
look at each other while they're [\h__\h]
the girl. And I think we can all agree,
what are we paying for?
>> [laughter]
>> I don't need the guys to [\h__\h] each
other, but listen, a hand on the back,
right? Like a little encouragement,
like, "You're killing it, king."
>> [laughter]
>> What happened to sportsmanship, right?
But then there's the other kind where
like everybody's [\h__\h] everybody. Like
they're all stacked on top of each other
like pancakes. Like guy, guy, girl,
insertion, insertion.
Even I saw that as a gay guy and I was
like, "Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> What happened to traditional family
values?"
I just want to apologize really quickly
cuz I kind of was thinking about it and
you know, I feel like I made a lot of
jokes about sucking off straight guys
and I don't
I don't want you guys to like leave here
and think that's like my thing or
whatever.
>> [laughter]
>> Or like that I'm trying to get that I
will just I wanted to clarify the only
porn I truly enjoy is usually titled
like um straight man forced [snorts] to
do something gay.
>> [laughter]
>> But I talked to my therapist about that
and she says it was because I was
bullied in high school by straight guys,
so now I get to watch it and be like,
"AND NOW WHO'S [\h__\h] GAY?"
>> [laughter]
>> THAT'S MY TIME. THANK YOU GUYS VERY
MUCH. GIVE IT UP FOR YOUR HOST.